Okay, recording is on.
Hello to future listeners.
For posterity,
the purpose of
this meeting is to
clarify the
specifications for
the entertainment
booking app,
which we at Acme
Corp are making for
the University
of Hindeburgh.
I'm Bobby from the
team at Acme Corp,
and here with me,
we have... Hi, I'm Cristina.
I work at the University
of Hindeburgh
as the Lead of the
Student Support Team.
Also another colleague
of mine, Jessica,
from the Student
Wellbeing
Department, was supposed
to be here with me,
but she wasn't
able to make it.
She left me some notes,
though, so hopefully
that would be enough.
Let's hope it is.
Okay, let's talk
about the app.
First off, can you give me
a rundown of its
basic functionality?
Certainly. The idea is
that various
entertainment providers,
which are businesses
like theatres,
cinemas, sports
places, and so on,
can register onto
the app and then
add their events
onto the app, too.
Then, students would also
be able to log in and
request a list of all of
the event performances
at a certain date,
choose specific
performances to
look at in more detail,
and book the performance
they're viewing
if they want to.
Okay, great. So let's
pick that apart
one by one.
You mentioned
entertainment providers
can register onto the app,
but in the written
spec we got,
you also mentioned
something about
verifying them by checking
a list. Can you elaborate?
Yes. We can't just
allow anyone with an
Internet connection to
say they're an
entertainment provider
offering events
to uni students.
There needs to be
some verification.
Makes sense. Okay.
But how do we do it?
Well, thankfully,
the university
already maintains an
up-to-date list
of approved
businesses for
other reasons,
so we could just use that.
We were intending to
just give you the list.
Okay. But how do
we then keep that
list updated?
Do you just send us
a new list every time
you make a change to it?
That could work, but it
wouldn't be
very efficient.
Hold on for a second.
Oh, yes. Here it
is in my notes
from our techs.
There's apparently
an API you can use
to directly ask
our system if
a specific entertainment
provider's
business number
is on the list.
If it is, you allow
the registration.
If not, don't allow
Okay. Yeah. So we just
use the API then.
Great. Okay, that
clears it up.
And then how
do you want to
do student registration?
Should there be a
similar system for that?
No, students would
be
pre-registered with their
university credentials,
and they would
just log in freely.
No need to check for them.
Okay. Understood.
Now, moving on
to the entertainment
provider
creating a new event
on the system.
I think for the most part,
we understand how
that should work,
except we weren't sure
about the way
tickets work.
In what way?
So when a student books
a ticket on the app,
we would need
to notify the
entertainment
provider about it
because that way they can
update their logs of
who has bought tickets,
and they can also update
their count of
remaining tickets.
Surely, they
need to do that.
Okay, so you
could do that?
We could, but there
are issues with it.
We need some kind
of integration
with every entertainment
provider's own
ticketing system,
and that's
problematic since
every one of their systems
will be different.
Alternatively,
we could come up
with some general
solution,
but then that
would likely be
very limiting in some
other ways, probably.
Actually, you don't
need to do that.
Part of the deal with
the entertainment
providers would
be that they
reserve tickets
to use just on our system.
These are separate from
any other tickets they may
be selling themselves.
So they wouldn't
need to update
their remaining
ticket count
at all when someone
books on the app.
Okay. So just to
check if I understand
correctly,
the entertainment
provider just
specifies the number of
tickets for each
performance.
And after that, we just
handle it entirely
on our own system,
and we don't even have to
communicate with them
at all after that.
Yes. Exactly. Yeah.
Okay. Yeah. That does
make things a lot
easier. Yeah.
I'm glad.
Okay. Now, next point.
When students request
the list of performances,
they specify a date
and get a list of
performances on that date.
What should students see
in that list of
performances?
Just some basic info,
like the event name,
the time and venue
of the performance,
who is the one providing
the event... I guess
that's enough.
Okay. And I assume
they should see
all available
info when they
look at a specific
performance.
Yes, indeed.
But this reminds me.
We talked about
an additional
feature we wanted
that I believe isn't in
the specification
we sent you.
Did we talk about students
being able to
choose preferences?
Preferences? No.
There wasn't
anything like
that in the spec.
Okay. What's the
idea with that?
The idea is that students
should be able to specify
preferences regarding
performances somehow.
And whenever they get
the list of performances,
it will prioritise ones
that match their
preferences.
Okay. Yeah, that
sounds like a
very good idea.
Okay. How would
they specify their
preferences,
and how would
the prioritisation
work exactly?
Well, to be honest,
I'm not sure.
It was a spur-of-the-moment idea
Jessica had,
but she's not
here, so... Okay.
Do we then organise
a meeting at
some later date
with Jessica
so we can talk
about the details?
Unfortunately,
Jessica won't be
back any time soon,
so I don't think
that's an option.
And anyways, for
things like this,
we're happy for you to go
with what students
would like.
Maybe ask them how
they feel about
it and implement it
based on what they want.
Okay. Yeah, we'll do that.
Yeah, we were
actually planning
to organise
something like that...
Sorry to interrupt!
I must shortly run
to another meeting,
and there's more
we need to cover.
Did you have any other
questions on your end?
Sure. We have one
more question.
Regarding booking,
how do we handle when
students book
performances for
non-ticketed events? How
does that even work?
Well, they should
only be able to
book ones for
ticketed events.
The non-ticketed ones
shouldn't require or
even allow bookings.
Okay. Got you. Right.
That's everything
on our end.
Was there anything
else you wanted
to talk about that
we haven't covered?
Yes. Jessica was really
insistent that we include
a review system
for the events so
students know how much
they were enjoyed.
Okay. That sounds
reasonable as well.
Did Jessica say how she
expects it to work,
or did she leave
anything in the notes?
Not really. It just
says "Reviews!!!" with
three exclammation
marks and with
a little arrow pointing to
it saying "Keep it simple".
I guess you could just
ask students to give
a review for
the performance
after the
performance happens?
A review for the performance
or for the event
overall? Because
the performance
will have ended by then...
Oh, yes, you're right.
Maybe for the event
overall makes more
sense in that case...
But what if an event has
performances with
different performers,
some better than others?
How would students
distinguish ratings in
this case? I don't know...
Yeah. That's a
good question.
There might be
some simple way
to do it, though.
If you want, we
could try to do
some research
regarding that
with the students, if
that's okay with you.
Sorry. Oh, sure.
Yes, let's say that.
Implement review somehow,
but keep it simple:
a rating and a comment, and
students seeing the
average rating somewhere.
Okay. Yeah, we'll
look into that. Yeah.
I'm really sorry, but
I really need to go now.
I hope this
meeting was useful
and helped you understand
what we want from the app!
Yeah, it definitely did.
Thanks for your
time, Cristina.
Thank you! Okay, bye!
Bye! Okay. Who even
thinks it's a good idea to
schedule a ten-minute
meeting for this?
It's way not enough.
Oh, whoops!