see so you just kept up to date and let me get my questions and are you guys ready?
okay start
so for the students review part is the rating could be like one to five star or simple like or dislike
so when a performance that i have booked has passed or i've attended as well i'd like to be able to
leave a review for it this should include a compulsory one to five rating and an optional
free text field this should become a review for its event which also mentions that performance
that i have attended as well okay yeah now our second option is for tickets that are fully sponsored
for free is it still necessary to call an external payment interface or can the reverse reservation
number be issued directly by the app
so are you talking about when it's fully covered from the sponsor yeah so as a student i don't know
the answer uh but they should probably get an automatic reference that's a good idea yeah
okay okay okay i have my own personal preference
can the can the ep just give an address of performance like a pending a pending status like
they're going to give a specific address but we will give it like before the performance
did you repeat that question yeah can the ep provide the address as pending
and they can modify the address before the performance like one day before just give the actual address
so i can't answer that as a student because that's the ep's job but i would say that's a good idea yes
yes okay and what's the um can the entertainment provider see the uh all the contact details of the
audience or just can see the email address or and their name so once again i can't answer that but my
preference would be um if the user gives consent to other information about them then yes but i would say
only be email and their name do you want to have a preference feature like uh like the event provider
should be required to tag performance with a certain amount of relevant keywords from a
predetermined list so students could be then select them select like which tags they are interested in
and the system would display events in order to match the tags so yeah so for that performance
you'd have a preference for that performance right yeah and that would be up to three event types such
as music movie or sports and you can also choose no preferences at all when you're searching up so
that would probably yes that would be a tagging feature that they would implement
so when you're reviewing when you're viewing the reviews is that what was that your question yeah
when requesting a list of performances for each one i'd like to see the average rating from all the reviews
for that specific event uh then when i look at a specific performance in addition to all the usual
information i'd see i should also be able to see the both the average rating and that individual review
as well with performance that it was about the review rating and that optional comment field as well
yeah and another question can subsidy be increased or decreased can what be subsidy or subsidy and i guess
sponsor sponsor um so that's as a student i don't know the answer but i would say probably yeah
yeah but i can't give a specific answer to that unfortunately
what specific details do you want students to see when looking at the specific performance
uh that has so at that performance that's already happened or that you're trying to go to you're trying to go to
okay
um i want to ask about the details that you can edit when there's no booking can you edit the price
so um so as a student i don't know the answer to that but the ep should be able to change the time
and the booking date as well but i don't know the specifics on the other side
okay thank you very much thank you no problem